family home. It may not be a $2.5 million home like yours, but that sounds like a lot of red
tape to me. Excuse me. Do you disagree? I really take that as a personal assumption. Do you disagree?
My home. Do you disagree that this was an overreach? I disagree that you're casting
expressions on me or my. Mr. Chairman, I yield. Thank you. Okay, so this is where we're going to
start, Ms. Kaskin. First of all, let me apologize because that was uncalled for. So let me do what
she would never do, which is to be an adult in this room. I'm also going to start with some
nonsense that she was trying to spew, and unlike Ms. Boebert, I am legally trained.
That's gonna hurt. In a verbal mismatch for the ages, fast-rising Texas Democrat Jasmine Crockett
faced off with Colorado Republican Lauren Boebert in what turned out to be a mismatch akin to any of
the following. Mayweather versus Jake Paul, Pete Brady versus any recent Browns team, or simply me
versus The Sun. This committee runs my pressure up, and I do come prepared to committee, and then
there's always somebody from this side that does something ridiculous that throws me all the way
off. Yes, it simply didn't end well for Boebert. Now, she got her hearing underway, as Republicans
tend to do, with fallacious remarks sprinkled with some ad hominem for good measure.
Family home. It may not be a 2.5 million dollar home like yours, but that sounds like a lot of red
tape to me. Excuse me, I really take that as a personal assumption. Do you disagree? My home. Do you disagree
that this was an overreach? I disagree that you're casting aspersions on me or my—
Ms. Katzen, my time has expired. Mr. Chairman, I yield. Thank you.
The lady's time has expired. Mr. Chairman, could we just ask all of our good members to respect the
civility and decorum and the integrity of the witnesses who've come forward at their own expense
to testify before us today? And an insult is not a substitute for an argument. I yield back to you.
The chair would advise the members to adhere to the House standard of decorum and proceed in order.
Ms. Crockett of Texas is recognized for five minutes.
And when it was Ms. Crockett's turn to take the floor, she reminded everyone just how different both
sides are.
Ms. This committee runs my pressure up. And I do come prepared to committee, and then there's always
somebody from this side that does something ridiculous that throws me all the way off.
So, oh, Jesus. Okay, so this is where we're going to start, Ms. Kaskin. First of all, let me apologize
because that was uncalled for. So let me do what she would never do, which is to be an adult in this
room or in this chamber. So let me start there. I'm also going to start with some nonsense that she
was trying to spew. And unlike Ms. Boebert, I am legally trained, and I've passed a few bar exams,
and I also legislated before I got here. So I do want to start with correcting the record a little bit.
And if you want to add to that, please do. There was conversation about ATF, because my colleagues
love to talk about their guns, baby. And I'm from Texas. So let me be clear. I also own firearms.
Let me screw. Democrats own guns, too. Let me make it clear. I own guns, and I'm licensed to carry.
That is a regulation. Regulations aren't necessarily bad. It didn't stop me from being able to get a gun.
So we were talking about, or y'all were talking about the ATF, which I wasn't going there. I didn't
plan to go there. But you know what? I honestly wish the ATF would run amok, because we know that
seemingly the people that run this chamber don't have the courage to come up with one of the things
we've heard is common sense regulations when it comes to guns. And to be clear, our Constitution,
the Second Amendment anticipates people having common sense. Unfortunately, we have not done
that. And unfortunately, it has cost us lives. So when you were testifying a little bit earlier,
you talked about unintended consequences. And the fact that we are supposed to be able to
anticipate that as lawmakers when we are writing laws. Unfortunately, not only have we ignored the
unintended consequences, but we've got foreseeable consequences that are continually ignored. And
that is why we are talking about regulation, at least on this side. So let's talk about my state,
because we always got good stuff coming out out of Texas. Unfortunately, my state decided that it
didn't want to be a part of the overall national grid, because my state did not want to deal with
all of the quote unquote, red tape. The cost of that was lives. So we had this winter storm.
And here it was, I was freshly being sworn into the Texas house. And I don't know what I'm supposed
to do, because I started getting calls because there is this thing called climate change. Hello,
nobody's in the chamber on the other side. But climate change is this real thing. And so in Texas,
we had this terrible storm that took place. And even though we are an energy capital, not just in
this country, but in the world, for clean and dirty energy, unfortunately, we couldn't keep our own
lights on. And it was all because they wanted to avoid red tape. You know what the cost of that was?
It was human lives. And I think that that's what being what's being lost. You know what happened in
Palestine or East Palestine? The cost was human lives. Unfortunately, seemingly, some people don't
want to consider human lives as an actual cost. The only cost that they ever talk about is dollars.
Well, let me be clear. I'm not here because of corporate dollars. I'm here because of people.
It's not the first, nor will it be the last time the new democratic star makes headlines for her
scathing retorts. In the past two hearings, she's came with CVS length receipts.
Okay, because Georgia purged 87,000. Will the gentlewoman yield? I think Georgia matters.
I will not yield. I am reclaiming my time. This country, we haven't had half as many hearings
about guns as we've had on voting rights. And every time we seemingly have a hearing on voting rights,
we talking about the fact that people are cheating. So let's talk about who's cheating. I got a few
articles. Are you familiar with the fact that there was recently a settlement with this little news
company called Fox News? Yes. Oh, okay. That was for about 780 something million dollars. Was it
because they were lying about the elections? Yes, it was for a... Okay, there we go. I'm running out of
time. So I'm gonna keep going. There also was this article because I don't want us to base anything on
Georgia at all. Please, Jesus, not Georgia. Okay, because Georgia purged 87,000. Will the gentlewoman
yield? I think Georgia matters. I will not yield. I am reclaiming my time. All right. So there were
87,000 people that were purged that were legitimate voters. So no, we don't want to copy off of Georgia.
Also, another GOP voter admits he committed fraud. Another one in Pennsylvania, man who admits he voted
for Trump with his dead mom's name because he listened to too much propaganda.
The gentlelady's time has expired. And not only does this instance demonstrate the sheer mass
between both parties, I mean, Bulbert didn't even have the respect to hear the opposite side's point
of view after throwing her snide insult and then leaving, which is on par for the party of family
values. As both Crockett and Raskin pointed out, they resort to insults because they have no argument.
They testify before us today. An insult is not a substitute for an argument.